[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '伝統文化' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "でんとうぶんか"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '娯楽' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ごらく"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '茶道' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お茶' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おちゃ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '道' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みち"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '書道' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '歌舞伎' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かぶき"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '能' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "のう"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '文楽' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぶんらく"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '相撲' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すもう"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '柔道' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅうどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '剣道' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんどう"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '空手' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "からて"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '漫才' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まんざい"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '落語' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "らくご"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji '囲碁' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いご"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the kanji '将棋' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the kanji '盆踊り' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぼんおどり"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the kanji '踊り' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おどり"
    }
]